Guide to the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBCJA), Local 132 Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBCJA), Local 132 archives
- Administrative Files, 1903-2004 and undated; 12.50 linear feet
  - Correspondence, 1925-1977; 1.25 linear feet
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1967 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1968 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, October 1, 1968 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1969 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1970 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1971 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1972 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1974 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1975 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1976 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1977 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- Correspondence, 1977 (Folder 6.0)
  - General Administrative Files, 1936-2004 and undated; 6.75 linear feet
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Ballots, 1936-1948, 1961-1982 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Calvert Hill Nuclear Power, undated (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Local 132 By-Laws, 1985 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Logo Work Order, 1990 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Metro Map, March 1, 1968 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Miscellaneous, undated (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Pension and Retirement, January 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Room Use, 1970-1971 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Special Election, April 3, 1974 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Trust Funds, 1994 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprentice Correspondence, 1998 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Graduation Dinner, 1998 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Arrears, 1998 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Bailey and Bailey, 1998 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Banks, 1998 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Bond &Tax Reports, 1998-1999 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- By-Law Changes, 1998-1999 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Carpet and Combined Funds, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Change of Status and Reinstatements, 1998 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Charges Against Delegate Election, 1997-1999 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Christmas Party, 1998 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Copy of Bills, 1998 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Correspondence in General, 1998 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Dinners, 1998 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- District Council Correspondence, 1998 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- District Council Minutes, 1998 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- District Council New Members, 1998 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- District Council Reports, 1998 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Donations, 1998 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Fifty-Year Members, 1998 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 1998 (Folder 14.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Insurance, 1998 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Kings Dominion, 1998 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters from General Office, 1998 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Received in General, 1998 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters to Apprentice School, 1998 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters to General Office, 1998 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Maryland and Delaware State Council, 1998 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Merrill Lynch, 1998 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Minutes, 1998 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Miscellaneous, 1998 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Officers and Delegate Expenses, 1998 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Pension Plan, 1998 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Pins and Certificates, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Quarterly Reports, 1998 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Supplies Purchased, 1998 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Trust Funds, 1998 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Time Sheets, 1998 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Work Hour Cards, 1998 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Active Work Cards, 2000 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Address Changes, 2000 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprentice Graduation Dinner, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Correspondence, 2000 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Letters Mailed, 2000 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Bailey and Bailey, 2000 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Change of Status, 2000 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Christmas Party, 2000 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- District Council Reports, 2000-2001 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Elections, 2000 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Fifty-Year Members, 2000 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 2000 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 2000 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Convention, 2000 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Mailed, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Received, 1999-2000 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Kings Dominion, 2000 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Mailed In General, 2000 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Received in General, 2000 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Minutes, 2000 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Pins and Certificates, 2000 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Quarterly Reports, 2000 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- 1st Quarter Receipts, 2000 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- 2nd Quarter Receipts, 2000 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- 3rd Quarter Receipts, 2000 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- 4th Quarter Receipts, 2000 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Correspondence, 2000 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Letters Mailed, 2000 (Folder 14.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Minutes, 2000 (Folder 15.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council New Members, 2000 (Folder 16.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Correspondence, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Graduation Dinner, 2001 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Letters Mailed, 2001 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Bailey and Bailey Audit Report, June 30, 1999 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- By-Law Changes, 2001-2002 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Change of Status, 2001 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Christmas Party, 2001 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Donations, 2001 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Elections, 2001-2002 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Fifty-Year Members, 2001 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 2001 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Kings Dominion, 2001 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Mailed, 2001 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Received, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Mailed In General, 2001 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Received in General, 2001 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Minutes, 2001 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Pins and Certificates, 2001 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Quarterly Reports, 2001 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Correspondence, 2001 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Correspondence, July 2001 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Letters Mailed, 2001 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council New Members, 2001-2002 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Reports, 2001 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Summary, 2001 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Supplies Purchased, 1999-2001 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Applications, 2002 (Folder 14.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Graduation Dinner, 2002 (Folder 15.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Letters Mailed, 2002 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Banks, 2002 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Bond and Tax Reports, 2001-2003 and undated (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Bond and Tax Reports, 2002 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Change of Status, 2002 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Christmas Party, 2002 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Copy of Bills, 2002 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Donations, 2002 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Environmental Information, 2002 and undated (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Fifty-Year Members, 2002 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 2002 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Mailed, June 2002 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Received, 2002-2003 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Reports, 2002 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Insurance, 2002 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Kings Dominion, 2002 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters in General, 2002 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Received in General, 2002 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Merrill Lynch, 2002 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Merrill Lynch, 2002-2003 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Minutes, 2002 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Miscellaneous, 2002 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Officers and Delegate Expenses, 2002-2003 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Pins and Certificates, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Quarterly Reports, 2002-2003 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Correspondence, 2002 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council New Members, 2002-2003 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Reports, 2002 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Time Sheets, 2002 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Trust Funds, 2002-2003 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- UNET, 2002 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Women's Conference, 2002 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Correspondence, 2003 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Graduation Dinner, 2003 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Apprenticeship Letters Mailed, 2003-2004 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Change of Status and Reinstatements, 2003 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Christmas Party, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Donations, 2003 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Elections, 2003 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Fifty-Year Members, 2003 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 2003 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Mailed, 2003 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Received, 2003 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Kings Dominion, 2003 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Mailed In General, 2003 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Received in General, 2003 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Meeting Attendance, 2003 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Meeting Attendance/Jackets, 2003 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Minutes, 2003 (Folder 13.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Pins and Certificates, 2003 (Folder 14.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Quarterly Reports, 2003 (Folder 15.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Correspondence, 2003 (Folder 16.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council New Members, 2003 (Folder 17.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Reports, 2003 (Folder 18.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Applications for Illness or Injury Disablement, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 1.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Change of Status and Reinstatements, 2004 (Folder 2.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 2004 (Folder 3.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Funeral Donations, 2004 (Folder 4.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Received, 2004 (Folder 5.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- General Office Letters Received, April 23, 2004 (Folder 6.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Kings Dominion, 2004 (Folder 7.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Mailed In General, 2004 (Folder 8.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Letters Received in General, 2004 (Folder 9.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Meeting Attendance, 2004 (Folder 10.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Minutes, 2004 (Folder 11.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Minutes, 2004 (Folder 12.0)
    - Administrative Files -- General -- Regional Council Correspondence, 2004 (Folder 13.0)
  - Financial Files, 1956-1989; 0.50 linear feet
    - Financial Records -- Accounts Receivable Record Book, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1.0)
    - Financial Records -- Bailey and Bailey, 1969 (Folder 2.0)
    - Financial Records -- Contingent Fund, 1964-1969 (Folder 3.0)
    - Financial Records -- Contingent Fund, 1969-1975 (Folder 4.0)
    - Financial Records -- Contingent Fund, 1976-1981 (Folder 5.0)
    - Financial Records -- Contingent Fund, 1981-1983 (Folder 6.0)
    - Financial Records -- Contingent Fund, 1984-1989 (Folder 7.0)
    - Financial Records -- Executive Board, 1963 (Folder 8.0)
    - Financial Records -- Petty Cash Record Book, 1977-1978 (Folder 9.0)
    - Financial Records -- Sixth Floor Expeditures, 1978-1979 (Folder 10.0)
    - Financial Records -- Welfare Fund, 1956 (Folder 11.0)
- Membership Files, 1910-2007 and undated; 11.50 linear feet
  - Membership Files -- Admitted on C. C. and Deaths, January 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1910 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1911 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1911 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1912 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1912 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1913 (Folder 7.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1914 (Folder 8.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1915 (Folder 9.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1917 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1917 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1917 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1917 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1918 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1918 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1918 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1918 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1920 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1921 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1922 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1922 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1924 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1925 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1925 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1926 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1927-1928 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1929-1930 (Folder 7.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1931-1933 (Box 31, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1934-1935 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1936-1937 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1937-1938 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1939 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1940 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1940 (Folder 7.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1940 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1941 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1941 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1941 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1942 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1942 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1942 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1942 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1942 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1943-1945 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1946 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1946 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1948 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1948 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1949 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1950 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1952-1953 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1954-1955 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1956 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1957-1958 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1959 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1961 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1962 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1963 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1964 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1966 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1966 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1967 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1968 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1968 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1969 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1970 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1970 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1971 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1972 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1973 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1973 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1973 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1974 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1974 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1974 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1975-1976 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1977-1978 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1979 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1980 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1982-1983 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1984 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1985 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1985 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1986 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1986 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1987 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1987 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1988 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1988 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1989 (Folder 7.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1989 (Folder 8.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1991 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1998 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 1999 (Folder 4.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 2000 (Folder 5.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications, 2000 (Folder 6.0)
  - Membership Files -- Applications (Blank), undated (Folder 7.0)
  - Membership Files -- Change of Status, 1979 (Folder 8.0)
  - Membership Files -- Change of Status, 1979 (Folder 9.0)
  - Membership Files -- Change of Status, 1980-1982 (Folder 10.0)
  - Membership Files -- Change of Status, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 1.0)
  - Membership Files -- Change of Status, 1985-1989 (Folder 2.0)
  - Membership Files -- Change of Status, 1994 (Folder 3.0)
  - Membership Files -- Clearance Cards and Deaths, 1974-1975 (Folder 4.0)